

Mbianou Toussom Colbert Bradon

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

CONTACT

P +237 671-242-032

E mbianoubradon@gmail.com

A Miss Bright Street Buea -Cameroon

Po mbianoubradon.vercel.app

EDUCATION

University of Buea 2019-2023

Bachelor of Engineering: Computer Engineering

University of Buea 2018-2021

Bachelor of Science: Biochemistry

SUMMARY

Knowledge enthusiastic engineer, who is a solution-oriented and problem solver with experience in building and maintaining quality software and software architecture.

Possess incredible leadership skills and love for people. Always ready to listen, learn, unlearn and relearn for team progress. Also, is highly skilled in communication, collaboration and Technical documentation

EXPERIENCE

Iknite Space

Software Engineer / May 2023- present

Positively supported the team's plans, goals and culture and active in the development of the WHOGET application, an application who links service render and those who needs services.

- Implementation of Mobile app frontend using React native.
- Implementation of Google and Facebook authentication with firebase
- Implementation of Admin web Dashboard using NextJS, TypeScript and TailwindCSS

Iknite Space

Software Engineering Intern / Nov 2022 - Apr 2023

Studied and practiced building of REST APIs with NodeJS, ExpressJS. Designed Front-End Mobile applications with React Native

- Analysis, Design and implementation of Portfolio Management system using ReactJS, Typescript and Firebase.
- Design and implement Fitness App using React Native and MongoDB

SKILLS

FRONT-END DEVELOPMENT HTML, CSS, Javascript, ReactJS,

NextJS, TailwindCSS,

BOOTSTRAP

BACK-END DEVELOPMENT NodeJS, ExpressJS, FIREBASE,

MONGODB

CROSS PLATFORM MOBILE React Native

APP DEVELOPMENT

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGE Typescript, Javascript, RUBY

MICROSOFT OFFICE Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Publisher,